Many organizations are shifting their project portfolios
‫‫- بسیاری از سازمان‌ها کارهای پروژه ‏
to Agile frameworks.
‫خود را به چهارچوب چابک منتقل می‌کنند.‏ ‏
However, even as the transition is taking place,
‫‫با این حال، حتی با وجود ‏
traditional methods remain.
‫گذار، روش‌های سنتی باقی مانده است.‏ ‏
In fact, in many cases both Agile
‫‫در حقیقت، در بسیاری از موارد هم روش چابک ‏
and traditional project methods continue to exist together.
‫و هم روشهای سنتی پروژه در کنار هم وجود دارند.‏ ‏
But knowing how to do that effectively can be a challenge.
‫‫اما دانستن نحوه انجام این کار به طور مؤثر می‌تواند یک چالش باشد.‏ ‏
In fact, a lot of people think
‫‫در حقیقت، بسیاری از مردم فکر می‌کنند که ‏
they can't even exist together at all.
‫اصلاً نمی‌توانند در کنار هم وجود داشته باشند.‏ ‏
However, in this course we compare Agile
‫‫با این حال، در این دوره چارچوبهای پروژه ‏
and traditional project frameworks.
‫چابک و سنتی را با هم مقایسه می‌کنیم.‏ ‏
We investigate the criteria you should use as you choose
‫‫ما معیارهایی را که باید انتخاب کنید ‏
which is the right method for your project.
‫روش مناسب برای پروژه خود را بررسی می‌کنیم.‏ ‏
We all want to be effective project leaders
‫‫همه ما می‌خواهیم رهبران مؤثر ‏
in our organizations.
‫پروژه در سازمانهای خود باشند.‏ ‏
Organizational change can make that challenging.
‫‫تغییر سازمانی می‌تواند این چالش برانگیز باشد.‏ ‏
What we need to do is to understand the changes taking place
‫‫کاری که ما باید انجام دهیم این است که ‏
and the reasons behind them.
‫تغییرات در حال وقوع و دلایل آنها را درک کنیم.‏ ‏
Hi, I'm Kelley O'Connell.
‫‫سلام من Kelley O'Connell هستم.‏ ‏
I've been a traditional project manager,
‫‫من مدیر پروژه‌های سنتی بوده‌ام و اکنون ‏
and am now an Agile coach and transformation strategist.
‫مربی چابک مربی و استراتژیست تحول هستم.‏ ‏
I've been leading teams for more than 20 years.
‫‫من بیش از 20 سال است که هدایت تیم‌ها را بر عهده دارم.‏ ‏
I've also been leading organizations
‫‫من همچنین 10 سال در سازمان ‏
through Agile transitions for 10 years.
‫انتقال چابک رهبری سازمان‌ها را داشته‌‌ام.‏ ‏
Please join me on LinkedIn Learning
‫‫لطفاً با مطالعه روشهای تلفیق پروژه، ‏
as we explore blending project methods.
‫در LinkedIn Learning به من بپیوندید.‏ ‏